logopond.com 2019-12-09

# Logopond - Logo, Brand & Identity Inspiration

Created: June 13, 2010 | Modified: February 1, 2019

At Logopond we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, and websites offered by Logopond collectively, Logopond’s “services.” If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:cd@climaxdesigns.com)

**Information we collect and how we use it**

We may collect the following types of information: 

**Information you provide** – When you sign up for a [Logopond Account](http://logopond.com/members/?account) we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password).

**Cookies** – When you visit Logopond, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences. We measure visitors to our websites and products using [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/analytics/web/). This service records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. We [anonymize the data in Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) – so we don’t know who you are; just that  _somebody_  visited our site. The information we collect helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better. You can learn more about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics' privacy policy") or [opt out if you wish](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "How to opt out of Google Analytics"). Google Analytics data is automatically deleted 26 months after your last visit. 

Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: 

<https://freestar.io/>  
<http://www.google.com/adsense/>

**Log information** – When you access Logopond, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**User communications** – When you send email or other communications to Logopond, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve Logopond. 

**Links** – Logopond may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed.

**Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to Logopond only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as advertisments, sites that include Logopond imagery or links from within their various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Logopond only processes personal information - but does not publicly display it - for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

  * Improving our site, including the display of customized content; 
  * Protecting the rights or property of Logopond or our users; and 
  * Developing new services. 

Logopond processes personal information on servers in the United States of America. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Logopond features may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. You can decline to submit personal information to Logopond at registration, in which case you may not be able to access Logopond.

**Information sharing**

Logopond only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Logopond in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Logopond, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If Logopond becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated non-personal information, such as the number of users, for example, or how many users clicked on particular content. Such information does not identify you individually. 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Logopond employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve the site. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Data integrity**

Logopond processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our site or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use Logopond, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. 

**Enforcement**

Logopond regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Logopond’s treatment of personal information by [contacting us](mailto:logopondnoreply@gmail.com)

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Logopond’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Logopond and an individual. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
